<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ArrayOfChangelogEntry xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon</Version>
    <Title>Better settings</Title>
    <Description>The Settings page was rushed before the release. It will be improved and will include more settings.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon</Version>
    <Title>Startup time optimization</Title>
    <Description>Houhou can be a bit slow to start. I'll be sure to check this soon.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon</Version>
    <Title>Database optimization</Title>
    <Description>I'm not satisfied with the speed of vocab search. I'll check this out as soon as possible.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon</Version>
    <Title>Keyboard shortcuts</Title>
    <Description>They should have been there already. There will be shortcuts to navigate to each tab, to start searching for a new Kanji, for vocab, SRS, etc.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon</Version>
    <Title>SRS items import/export</Title>
    <Description>From the SRS page, you will be able to import batches of SRS items in the application, or export your current list.
Both the import and export features will support multiple formats.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon</Version>
    <Title>Web synchronization</Title>
    <Description>You will be able to synchronize your SRS items with an account on the website.
This will make it easier to use Houhou on multiple devices.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Soon?</Version>
    <Title>Fill the blank in the SRS tab</Title>
    <Description>There's nothing to cover the bottom of the SRS tab. Maybe I'll add a graph or something.
I'm open to your ideas on this.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Later</Version>
    <Title>Radical set and SRS Level set editors</Title>
    <Description>Right now, Radical sets and SRS Level sets have to be created and modified by hand in XML.
In the future, you will be able to edit those easily and safely from the Settings tab.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Later</Version>
    <Title>Complete SRS filters</Title>
    <Description>A more complex version of the SRS item filters in the SRS items browsing page is planned.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Maybe later</Version>
    <Title>Kanji drawing order</Title>
    <Description>Maybe the application could display the Kanji drawing order from the Kanji details page. I need to investigate this to be sure this is possible with open resources.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>Maybe later</Version>
    <Title>Kanji drawing filter</Title>
    <Description>The ability to search for Kanji by drawing them would be a great feature but would probably require a lot of work.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
</ArrayOfChangelogEntry>