<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ArrayOfChangelogEntry xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Export feature</Title>
    <Description>You can now export any selection of SRS items in the Item Browsing part of the SRS tab.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>WaniKani import feature</Title>
    <Description>You can now import your items from WaniKani in the import menu.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Next review date editing</Title>
    <Description>You can now edit the next review date of any item individually in its edition window.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Auto-skip option</Title>
    <Description>A new option under Settings > SRS allows you to automatically skip to the next question upon entering a correct answer.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Minor additions and fixes</Title>
    <Description>• Vocab with an outdated reading now appear on a semi-transparent gray background.
• The 60 character limit on the kanji writing field for vocab SRS items has been lifted.
• Typing "_" in kana fields will now input a "ー".
• Fixed SRS item modification during reviews causing spaces to appear between their meanings.
• Fixed Houhou crashing when using items above the maximal SRS level.
• Fixed a crash occuring for some users when using the "Copy" button in vocab lists.
• Fixed a selection bug occuring when navigating through kanji by clicking characters in a vocab list.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.1</Version>
    <Title>New ignore shortcuts setting</Title>
    <Description>Added an SRS setting to enable some new shortcuts during reviews to ignore a submitted answer.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.1</Version>
    <Title>Small SRS items browsing improvements</Title>
    <Description>SRS item browsing now has slightly improved filters and performs better.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.1</Version>
    <Title>Minor additions and fixes</Title>
    <Description>• During reviews, meaning questions now handle meanings with parenthesis expressions (e.g. "master (of a house)" will accept "master").
• Clicking a reading on a kanji page will now filter vocab using the clicked reading.
• Changed the SRS progress display on items to display the progression through your SRS levels.
• Changed the background color of the answer box after validating your answer during reviews to be more flashy.
• Typing "zz" in kana fields will now input the small tsu (っ).
• Typing "n'" in kana fields will now input a ん.
• Typing ca/ci/cu/ce/co in kana fields will now input か/き/く/け/こ.
• Fixed bulk SRS item edition with too many items.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1</Version>
    <Title>User folder modification</Title>
    <Description>New feature: you can now move your user folder wherever you want. For example, synchronize your SRS database by using a Dropbox folder.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1</Version>
    <Title>CSV import</Title>
    <Description>New feature: import SRS items from a CSV file.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.0.1</Version>
    <Title>Bugfix</Title>
    <Description>A minor bugfix release.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Title>Houhou is out!</Title>
    <Description>At last, Houhou is released.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
</ArrayOfChangelogEntry>