<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ArrayOfChangelogEntry xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.3</Version>
    <Title>Fixed audio issues</Title>
    <Description>After Windows 10's october 2018 update, trying to play an audio clip would crash Houhou.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.3</Version>
    <Title>WaniKani levels 51-60</Title>
    <Description>(Contribution by Larsie13 and shoaibshakeel381)
Houhou will now properly show vocab and kanji taught for levels 51 to 60 on WaniKani, and import your WaniKani items for these levels through the WaniKani import module.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.3</Version>
    <Title>Wrap Up</Title>
    <Description>(Contribution by Larsie13)
While doing reviews, there is now a 'Wrap up' button that ends the review session without a loss of data.
This means that all kanji and vocab of which the reading question has appeared in the session will get their meaning question soon and vice versa, but no new kanji and vocab will appear in this session.
(Note that since review items are scheduled in batches, items in the current batch of which neither the meaning nor reading has appeared will still appear in this session.)

This helps when you're in a hurry, or when you have 300 reviews and don't want to do all of them at once.

Note: The old behaviour of exiting the review immediately is still available through the little 'X' button next to it.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
   <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.3</Version>
    <Title>Shortcuts!</Title>
    <Description>(Contribution by Larsie13)
Many tasks can now be performed with the keyboard, no mouse needed! Check the help page for more information (under 'Efficiency tips...').</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.3</Version>
    <Title>Filter vocab/kanji by JLPT/WK level</Title>
    <Description>(Contribution by Larsie13)
You can now filter vocabulary words and kanji by the level at which they are taught on the Kanji learning website WaniKani and the JLPT level at which they are used.

Moreover, vocabulary words can now be filtered by their categories (such as mathematical terms and computer-related terms).</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Quick add for vocab</Title>
    <Description>You can now add vocab to your SRS list in one click using the Quick add button.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>New info for kanji and vocab</Title>
    <Description>The kanji details page now shows a new frequency rank, computed from a study of more than 7000 books; it also shows the drawing strokes of the kanji, its grade, its JLPT level and its level on WaniKani when appliable.
In a similar fashion, vocab shows frequency info from the books study, frequency rank from a study of Wikipedia articles, JLPT level and WaniKani level when appliable.
These data provide a great help in deciding which kanji or words you want to learn.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Vocab variants</Title>
    <Description>Vocabulary entries now show their variants (different writing, same or close meaning) when they exist. Keep in mind that variants are often less used than the main entries.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Audio support for vocab</Title>
    <Description>Added support for audio pronunciation of words. You have to configure this feature in the Settings/Vocab tab.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Furigana for vocab</Title>
    <Description>Instead of the old fashioned vocabulary entries with kanji on one column and kana on the other, kana now shows up as furigana for most entries.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Batch rescheduling/delay for your SRS items</Title>
    <Description>You can now reschedule or delay the next review date of multiple items at once using the "Browse" part of the SRS tab.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Optional meaning/reading field for SRS items</Title>
    <Description>You are no longer forced to fill both the Accepted meanings and the Accepted Readings fields. This means that you are now free to add a kana-only word without any accepted reading, so that the system doesn't prompt you to enter the reading of an item that already appears in all kana.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.2</Version>
    <Title>Minor additions and fixes</Title>
    <Description>• Settings are (hopefully) no longer overwritten when updating Houhou.
• Searching vocab by meaning is now (hopefully) a bit faster.
• Added settings on the kanji and vocab subtabs to define how many kanji and vocab are shown in result lists.
• Added a configurable setting that collapses vocabulary definitions in the result list when there are too many different meanings.
• The kanji characters of vocab entries that are usually written in kana now have a toned down opacity.
• Added proper credits to the resources Houhou uses on the bottom of this page.
• The button to copy the kanji reading of a vocab entry to the clipboard is now split in two; one button for kana, the other for kanji.
• The auto-fill arrow button on the SRS item creation/editing window is now slightly smarter.
• When a crash occurs, you can now open your log file, so that you can easily save it and send it to me.
• Added a clearer error label when trying to import items from WaniKani with an unsubscribed account.
• The tray app now (by default) shows a popup when closing the main window.
• Added a setting to completely shutdown Houhou (along with the SRS tray app) when closing the main window.
• Fixed the "SRS item edition" window title.
• Added a setting to show/hide nanori (name) readings for kanji. It is off by default.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Export feature</Title>
    <Description>You can now export any selection of SRS items in the Item Browsing part of the SRS tab.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>WaniKani import feature</Title>
    <Description>You can now import your items from WaniKani in the import menu.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Next review date editing</Title>
    <Description>You can now edit the next review date of any item individually in its edition window.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Auto-skip option</Title>
    <Description>A new option under Settings > SRS allows you to automatically skip to the next question upon entering a correct answer.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.2</Version>
    <Title>Minor additions and fixes</Title>
    <Description>• Vocab with an outdated reading now appear on a semi-transparent gray background.
• The 60 character limit on the kanji writing field for vocab SRS items has been lifted.
• Typing "_" in kana fields will now input a "ー".
• Fixed SRS item modification during reviews causing spaces to appear between their meanings.
• Fixed Houhou crashing when using items above the maximal SRS level.
• Fixed a crash occuring for some users when using the "Copy" button in vocab lists.
• Fixed a selection bug occuring when navigating through kanji by clicking characters in a vocab list.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.1</Version>
    <Title>New ignore shortcuts setting</Title>
    <Description>Added an SRS setting to enable some new shortcuts during reviews to ignore a submitted answer.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.1</Version>
    <Title>Small SRS items browsing improvements</Title>
    <Description>SRS item browsing now has slightly improved filters and performs better.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1.1</Version>
    <Title>Minor additions and fixes</Title>
    <Description>• During reviews, meaning questions now handle meanings with parenthesis expressions (e.g. "master (of a house)" will accept "master").
• Clicking a reading on a kanji page will now filter vocab using the clicked reading.
• Changed the SRS progress display on items to display the progression through your SRS levels.
• Changed the background color of the answer box after validating your answer during reviews to be more flashy.
• Typing "zz" in kana fields will now input the small tsu (っ).
• Typing "n'" in kana fields will now input a ん.
• Typing ca/ci/cu/ce/co in kana fields will now input か/き/く/け/こ.
• Fixed bulk SRS item edition with too many items.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1</Version>
    <Title>User folder modification</Title>
    <Description>New feature: you can now move your user folder wherever you want. For example, synchronize your SRS database by using a Dropbox folder.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.1</Version>
    <Title>CSV import</Title>
    <Description>New feature: import SRS items from a CSV file.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.0.1</Version>
    <Title>Bugfix</Title>
    <Description>A minor bugfix release.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
  <ChangelogEntry>
    <Version>1.0</Version>
    <Title>Houhou is out!</Title>
    <Description>At last, Houhou is released.</Description>
  </ChangelogEntry>
</ArrayOfChangelogEntry>